乐队注意  向前齐步走
十秒倒数开始
二  一  开始
Behati到位了
Doutzen在这
Adriana还有20秒
Ale在我这
第五个是Alessandra
给第七个来个特写  镜头到第七个
她转身时给个特写
-漂亮  -Lindsay  倒数第三位  第十个
-Lily到了  -这就来
Elsa开始走台
Karlie在这  Karlie候场
-Candice出场  -这可是价值千万的胸罩
让她上场  让她走  快点
我好紧张啊
后台谁负责首饰
准备让Taylor Swift从左侧登台
她来了
-开始  -第一位准备从六号门入场
上Fall Out Boy的布景
一切就绪  准备开始
-开始紧张了  -你看上去美极了
-看着就身价百万  -好极了
Bahati就在这  她来了  她来了
A Great Big World准备就绪
灯光全开
Neon Jungle准备好
三  二  一  开始
女士们先生们
掌声有请Fall Out Boy
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com
"Whoa, oh
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com
"Whoa, whoa
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com
"Whoa, oh
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com
"Whoa, whoa
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com
"B-B-Be careful making wishes in the dark, dark "
"Can't be sure when they've hit their mark and "
"Besides in the mean, meantime, I'm just "
"Dreaming of tearing you apart "
"I'm in the de-details with the Devil "
"The world can never get me on my "
"Level, I just got to "Get you off the cage,
I'm a young lover's rage "
"Gonna need a spark to ignite
"My songs know what you did "In the dark
"So light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, up, light 'em up, up "
"I'm on fire, light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up "
"Im 'on fire "
"Whoa, oh
"Whoa, whoa
"In the dark, dark
"Whoa, oh
"Whoa, whoa
"In the dark, dark
女士们先生们  有请Taylor Swift
"Writers keep writing what they write "
"Somewhere another pretty vein just died "
"I've got the scars from tomorrow and I wish "
"You could see that you're the antidote "
"To everything except for me
"A constellation of tears on your "
"Lashes burn everything you love then burn the "
"Ashes, in the end everything collides, my childhood "
"Spat back out the monster that you see "
"My songs know what you did in the " "Dark
"So light 'em up, up, up, light 'em " "Up, up, up,
light 'em up, up " 79 00:04: 00:04:08,047
"I'm on fire "
"Light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, up, light 'em "Up, up,
I'm on fire "
"Whoa, oh
"Whoa, whoa, in the dark, dark "
"Whoa, oh, whoa, whoa
"In the dark, dark
晚上好  纽约
欢迎来到《维多利亚的秘密时尚秀》
我是Taylor
他们是我的朋友  Patrick  Pete  Andy和Joe
他们是Fall Out Boy  而她们
是2013年维密天使
PATRICK STUMP: "My songs know what you did "In the dark...
"My songs know
"What you did in the "Dark...
"So light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, I'm on fire "
"Whoa, oh
"Whoa, whoa
"In the dark, dark
"Whoa, oh
"Whoa, whoa
"Light 'em up, up, up "
"Light 'em up, up, up,
light 'em " "Up, up, I'm on fire "
"Light 'em up " "Whoa, oh
"Whoa
"Whoa, oh, whoa
"Whoa.
太棒了
让我们把你领出去化妆做头发
细节出去弄
有人看见Kasia了吗
Behati在我这
我们需要Candice到标记处来
我看见她了  看见了  没问题
很好  Doutzen到了  我们准备好了
天使们准备就绪
准备登台
我觉得我从小到大
就一直在模拟天桥走秀
我第一次知道时尚秀时
我好像才四岁
我的梦想
就是参加维密时尚内衣秀
对于来自巴西小镇的我来说
这太了不起了
我就想成为那些女孩中的一员
加入这个不可思议的大家庭
我18岁时
我就定下目标
要参加维密时尚内衣秀
却不知道这意味着什么
我当时年纪小  缺乏安全感  很害怕
我来维密的第一件事
就是参加时尚内衣秀的模特选拔
很多人问我们
你们选拔都看重什么
对我们来说  最重要的是找到
热情向上  积极开朗的人
我们要找一位美丽健康的女性
我从没这么紧张过
把果冻和水泥混起来的感觉
-就是当时我腿的感觉  -慢点  慢点
这是个成为巨星的好机会
我当时很年轻  对我来说简直不可思议
我能够参加走秀  能够站上天桥
我见到了Heidi  Laetitia  Stephanie
还有Tyra Banks  Gisele  Adriana
天呐天呐  真不敢相信我居然在这
她们太美了
I never imagined that I would be on that runway.
我从未想过自己能参与维密内衣秀
"And we're gonna let it burn, burn, burn "
"Burn, we're gonna let it burn... "
My first time doing the VS Fashion Show,
第一次加入维密内衣秀
改变了我的模特生涯
维密能推动你的事业
提高了我的知名度
大家都知道你是谁
这是段无与伦比的旅程
岁月如梭
真希望时间能走得慢一点
我到现在都还没缓过神来  但我做到了
我成为了维密天使
I'm just one lucky girl.
我是位幸运的女孩
女士们先生们  掌声欢迎A Great Big World
"Say something, I'm giving up on you "
"I'll be the one if you want me to "
"Anywhere, I would've followed you "
"Say something
"I'm giving up on you "
"And I...
"Am feeling so small
"It was over my head
"I know nothing at all
"And I...
"Will stumble and fall
"I'm still learning to love "
"Just starting to crawl
"Say something
"I'm giving up on you "
"I'm sorry "
"That I couldn't get to you "
"Anywhere I would have followed you "
"Say something
"I'm giving up on you "
"And I...
"Will swallow my pride
"You're the one "
"That I love
"And I'm saying good-bye "
"Say something
"I'm giving up on you "
"And I'm sorry "
"That I couldn't get to you "
"And anywhere
"I would have followed you
"Oh...
"Say something
"I'm giving up on you "
"Say something.
Copy that! Nick, go!
收到  Nick快去吧
让Lily走  你先去帮忙
-让天使们过  -"迷海遗舰"马上开始
大伙们  翅膀来咯  借过
I don't know how it feels to be stuck on a deserted island.
我不知道被困在孤岛上是什么感觉
-我一定会喜欢  -我讨厌极了
我喜欢沙滩  也喜欢大海
要看谁与我同行
随便吧  这就行了  对吧
我会带着...
手机
冲浪板
烧烤炉
一把刀
一位强壮的男士
无线网络不能少
无线网络
卫星电话
-我的孩子和家人  -水
Should we build a fire"
需要生火吗
我能钻木取火  我可是非洲人呐
All right, we got nothin'.
算了  一点结果都没有
一定会很有乐趣的
带我离开这座岛
谁都不会来救我们
情况可能会更糟
我们至少还有彼此
麻烦给Taylor Swift换装
天呐
为下一环节做准备
准备下一环节
他们去楼下找Cara了
还在弄她的服装
还有Jourdan没找着人
广告过后  "巴黎之夜"即将登场
Only CBS.
精彩尽在CBS
Oh, my God!
天呐
我们以试衣模特为标准
制订走秀服装
许多试衣模特都成为了维密巨星
包括Ale  Lindsay和Candice
我可以试穿所有服装
试戴首饰和羽毛
服装的灵感令人惊喜
你们居然还有新点子
"Baby, in our wildest moment"..
This feels good. I like it.
这套不错  我喜欢
"We could be the greatest, baby, in our wildest mom秂nt
试衣模特不好当
你就像个衣架子
穿着半成品
任凭设计师裁剪  等他们完成服装
嗨  Barbara
Barbara Fialho是我们这几年的
试衣模特
她对一切充满了热情
She inspires us,
她鼓舞了我们
让大家工作都非常愉快
团队里能有Barbara这样的人
是非常重要的
这份工作棒极了
That's me. Oh, yeah.
这是我呀
去年是我的首秀  是个非常棒的经历
在那之后  我的生活改变了许多
我拿到了第一份化妆广告
参与了纪梵希的宣传活动
我的模特生涯更上了一层楼
-我们为你选了一套服装  -真的吗
你一定会喜欢
Oh, my God!
天呐
Oh, my God.
我一开始就看上了这个
你应得的
旅途继续
再见
Adriana准备  音乐五号
投影和灯柱准备好
Adriana在穿翅膀
她从舞台左侧进场
Adriana  还有20秒进场
MILEY CYRUS: "Oh, you broke my heart
"I told you
"I was weak for love
"But then you went around
"And did what you wanted to do "
"And now I'm crying "
"Crying
"Ooh, it seemed like everything was going fine "
"I found love that I thought was gonna last "
"Then I accidentally saw a few things in your cell "
"I even LOL'd "
"Man, I should've known "
"Why, why you do what you do"
"You, you might as well just tell the honest truth "
"See, I'm not really down with this "
"This ain't no texting "
"No, I got no biz, but it is what it is "
"I don't really have much to say "
"I was over it
"The second that I saw her name "
"I got two, two
"Two letters for you
"One of them's whoo! And the other one's "
"'Cause what you got to do is go get yourself a clue "
"Only two, two, two
"Letters to choose
"One of them's whoo! And the other one's "
"SMH, I'm pressing send on you "
"Could've been this, couldn't been that "
"We done been there, we done been back "
"You ain't with it, could've said that "
"Why you trippin', let me hear that "
"I ain't trying to argue all morning "
"I do it all for you
"You know you're my right eye "
368 00:20: 00:21:01,059 "Baby, let me show you
"Oh, I know what's been going on "
"Don't even try to act like Mr. Super Nonchalant "
"What makes you think I'll stick around "
"I'm not as stupid as you sound, and you "
"Sound really dumb right now
"From A to zed
"Ooh, ah
"I got a lot of nasty things
"Blowing up in my head
"But none of them are worth my time "
"You're not even worth this rhyme "
"And I don't, I don't "
"Give a flying
"I don't really have much to say "
"I was over it the second that I "
"Saw her name
"I got two
"Two, two letters "For you
"One of them's whoo! "
"And the other one's "
"'Cause what you got to do is go get yourself a clue "
"Only two, two, two
"Letters to choose
"One of them's whoo! And the other one's "
"Smh
"I'm pressing send on you "
"Ooh, ooh, two letters for you "
"Yeah "Letters for you "
"What you trippin' on, huh" "
"Girl, you know you're wrong, huh "
"Don't let these girls drive you crazy "
"I don't really have much to say "
"I was over it the second that I saw her name "
"I got two, ooh, ooh, letters for you "
"One of them's whoo! And the other one's "
"'Cause what you gotta do is go get yourself a clue "
"Only two, two, two, letters to choose "
"One of them's "
"And the other one's "
"SMH, I'm pressing send on you "
"I got two, two, two letters for you... "
停止排放干冰
Clyde  倒数60秒  撤下巴黎街灯
"'Cause what you gotta do "
"Is go get yourself a clue
"Only two, two, two, two...
"I'm pressing send on you. "
今年的假日广告是在巴黎拍的
开拍
犹如梦境一般
妙不可言
我们决定在夜间拍摄
午夜拍广告  感觉有些挑逗
从全新的视角来拍摄
内衣和天使们
我们睡了一白天  晚上八点才开始做造型
接着整晚都在拍广告
我们的生物钟的确与众不同
凌晨六点  我们还在香榭丽舍大街拍外景
当时我只穿着内衣
戴着翅膀走来走去  没啥大不了的
开拍
"I've been infected with restless "
"Whispers and cheats...
巴黎的夜晚灯火绚烂
它是光明之城
我们真的点亮了它的光芒
维密公司花下重金
让埃菲尔铁塔整晚闪烁
难以置信的美丽  特别和浪漫
"Thanit mafested...
我当时真是冻得要命
天上还下着雪
要是让我受冻
我就会不开心
这次的拍摄场面特别宏大
拍了许多动人心魄的美丽场景
是展现演技的好机会
为了展现性感  我通常会做这样的表情
这是搞怪版Behati
有点二的Behati
这是性感版Candice
这才叫性感
有何贵干
大概有一千多位娱记
想要拍到我们的照片
但广告拍摄依旧顺利
没什么能阻挡维密假日广告
Lais非常出色
她是我认识的最甜美
最温柔  最美丽的姑娘
我从没在天桥上摔倒过
但世事无常  一旦发生后果极其沉重
参加这个秀是每个女孩的梦想
我十分重视它
去年在彩排的时候
不知道怎么回事
我突然摔倒了
我觉得我的脚踝断了
恐惧感会一直萦绕在你脑海中
这件事真的特别可怕
在彩排中扭伤脚踝
然后无法参加走秀
这事太让人伤心了
好了
大家都吓坏了
因为他们说
看上去很严重
她的脚踝好像真的断了
我当然特别沮丧
我开始哭泣
当时的场面特别沉重
第二天  我醒来
试着站起来
还是不行
没法走路
我不得不
穿起她的装扮  替她走秀
那感觉太糟糕了
穿着她的装扮太难受了
因为那本是她的  不该由我去展现
今年  我做了更充足的准备
Lais  出来让我们看看吧
辣妹哟
试衣的时候
我告诉他们  如果我又摔倒
我一定会挥着翅膀飞起来
因为去年你出了意外  所以今年
我们希望你来走这个单元的开场
叫作"天堂飞鸟"
感谢你
抱歉
今晚  我无比兴奋和快乐
也很紧张
我希望Lais今年
能走一场最美妙的秀
穿最热辣的衣服
希望一切都如她所愿
我们都会在她身后支持她
为她欢呼
我一定会在后台支持她
祝她享受最美时刻
上吧
Fall Out Boy登台吧
" Fall Out Boy – "The Phoenix" "
"Put on your war paint
"You are a brick tied to me that's dragging me down "
"Strike a match and I'll burn you to the ground
姑娘  上吧
"We are the jack-o'-lanterns in July "
"Setting fire to the sky
"Here it comes this rising tide c, soome on "
"Put on your war paint
"Cross walks and crossed hearts and hope-to-dies "
"Silver clouds with gliray ning "
"So we can take the world back from a heart attack "
"One maniac at a time we will take it back "
"Time crawls on
"When you're waiting for the song to start "
"Dance alone to the beat of your heart "
"Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel "
"Like our time is running out" "
"I'm gonna change you like a remix "
"Then I'll raise you like a phoenix "
"It's our vintage misery "
"No, I think it looked a little better on me "
"I'm gonna change you like a remix "
"Then I'll raise you like a phoenix "
"Bring home the boys and scrap, scrap methtal e tanks "
"Get hitched, make a career out of robbing banks "
"Because the world is just a teller "
"And we are wearing black masks "
""You broke our spirit" Says the note we pass "
"Take the world back from a heart attack "
"One maniac at a time, we'll take it back "
"Time crawls on
"When you're waiting for the song to start "
"Dance alone to the beat of your heart "
"Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel "
"Like our time is running out" "
"I'm gonna change you like a remix "
"Then I'll raise you like a phoenix "
"It's our vintage misery "
"No, I think it looked a little better on me "
"I'm gonna change you like a remix "
"Then I'll raise you like a phoenix "
"The war is won before it's begun "
维密秀  欢呼声在哪里
"Release the doves, surrender love "
"The war is won before it's begun "
"Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! "
"Before it's begun "
"Release the dove "Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! "
"Surrender love "Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! "
"The war is won before it's begun "
"Rseelea d theoves "Wave the white f lag!"
"Wave the white flag! " "Surrender love
"Hey, young blood
"Doesn't it feel like our time is running out" "
"I'm gonna change you like a remix "
"Then I'll raise you like a phoenix. "
注意翅膀  小心点儿
这是我正常的样子
这是我性感的样子
等等  我都不知道我性感是什么样
矮油  我看起来性感吗
你确定吗
关键在头发
走秀风来一个
好样的
真的好好笑
这才是我性感的样子
下节精彩
Taylor Swift和Neon Jungle登场
双重惊喜哦
精彩尽在CBS
一  二  三  开始
《维密时尚内衣秀》下节精彩
更多美丽的维密天使登场
以及独一无二的Taylor Swift
维密时尚内衣秀
精彩尽在CBS
"Let's go "
"I wanna go around the world
"And party with the girls
" ' Le's go "
nd"A when I get there, wh gen Iet there "
"When I'm there I wanna go-o-o "
"Ina wan go crazy
"I wanna go
"I wanna go crazy
"That's where I wanna go "
"I wanna go cra-cra-cra-cra- cra-cra-crazy-zy-zy-zy-zy "
"We like to sleep all day...
维密时尚内衣秀
加入维密话题
"This is how we like to live our life "
"Hands up!
今晚这场秀里的
所有模特
其实都是社交媒体上的明星
发些东西到网上很好啊
"Let's go! "
我最开始接触的是Twitter
我从那里得到所有的消息
没有Instagram没法活啊
我觉得Facebook很棒
谁是爆照狂人
Cara
Cara.
不好意思
她在社交媒体上很有影响力
这很好啊
网络平台很自由
没有任何限制  畅所欲言
她特别大胆
我没考虑太多  想做什么就做什么
我喜欢她这态度
她们的粉丝多得吓人
我在Instagram上有290万粉丝
总共得有上千万的粉丝
我每隔三四分钟
就会拿起手机看看
每次打开手机  都会看到新的东西
我发的大多都关于
家庭  工作和慈善的东西
鼓舞人心的名人名言
积极向上的消息
有时我发了不该发的照片
我所拥有的一切
就可能立刻毁于一旦
就好像按了一个巨大的红色按钮
一切瞬间爆炸
小心哦
悔推  你不能发任何让你后悔的东西
我想我以前删过一些东西
但我不记得是什么了
-删除  -我还没碰到情况糟糕到
我得找我的经纪人  让他"快删掉"
Instagram蒙羞
生命苦短  没空在Instagram上蒙羞
随便去谷歌搜一搜
很容易就搜到我的屁股了
太疯狂了
咱们现在应该干点坏事儿
-我知道  有"助"形象  -没错
这个品牌在世界上如此闻名
也得益于她们那些社交活动
这也是工作的一部分
是吗
维密时尚内衣秀
准备  所有粉红女郎
请所有粉红模特到前台
这是我第一次走台
穿上这身美丽的衣服还有翅膀
真是无比荣幸
其他人为我第一次表演而紧张
这也让我很紧张
我没办法停止  我脸上
这傻乎乎的笑  我都笑了好几周了
Neon Jungle请到开场位置  马上
女士们先生们  掌声欢迎
无与伦比的Neon Jungle
T 秎eroub
"I don't look for troub le,but trouble looks for me "
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say, "Here comes a hurricane "
"Trouble is her middle name"
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, tre oubllooks for me "
" Heyhey
"I don't look for trouble "
"But trouble looks for me
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say, "Here comes a hurricane "
"Trouble is her middle name"
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me "
"Hey, hey
"I just want to live a quiet life "
"I'll make an excellent wife "
"Man, I swear I really try
"But some boys-- they just can't eat it whole "
"Trouble is my name, k younow
"Trouble is my name, you know "
"I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me "
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say, "Here comes a hurricane "
"Trouble is her middle name"
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me "
"Hey, hey
"Hey
"I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me "
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say that girl got so many sides "
"Uh, I'm a Gemini "
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me "
"Hey, hey
"Hey
"Lights up, let's have a toke " 791 00:45: 00:45:03,967
"Pour more whiskey in my Coke
"Never been one of the herd
"Flippin' everyone the bird "
"People say that I am heartless "
"I've just learned to use my heart less "
"I go hard 'cause I'm the hardest "
"And we ain't even started yet "
"Hey
"Hey, hey
"Trouble
"I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me "
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say, "Here comes a hurricane "
"Trouble is her middle name"
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me "
"Hey, hey, I don't look for trouble "
"But trouble looks for me
"And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 "
"They say, "Here comes a hurricane "
"Trouble is her middle name"
"But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me "
"Hey, hey
"Trouble.
谢谢
谢谢大家
Taylor来表演啦
好激动
她才华横溢
还那么美丽
Taylor是典型的美国女孩
她就像美国梦一样
我想我们一定会玩得很开心的
太棒了
-我们已经是好多年的朋友  -闺蜜
看到她在工作的同时
我也在工作
-我知道  -不可思议啊
那首《Trouble》
《Trouble》
广告之后  我的闺蜜Taylor Swift即将登台
要如何成为一位天使呢
竭尽全力
即使那样也还是不够
"I want your body, everybody wants your body "
"So let's jack, let's jack... "
这需要集中精力
需要下定决心  需要付出耐力
但缺乏力量的美是空洞的
这些姑娘的训练堪比专业运动员
她们为了梦想的身材而努力锻炼
Michael让我像拳手一样训练
而且这场战斗永无止境
我为走秀而锻炼
I work out for the runway, but mostly I work out for life.
但更多时候是在为自己的人生而锻炼
Adriana有真本事
我为她制定的体能训练十分疯狂
她的劲头势不可挡
"Jack, jacack, jk, jack
"Jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack... "
我喜欢大汗淋漓
"Everybody wants your body...
我喜欢运动不止
当我爱上某种东西  我会全情投入
你跟Adriana一起走
候场了  Adriana
Taylor来了  候场
Behati到位
她到了  她到了
Taylor就位
请她上台  有请Taylor Swift
女士们先生们  请热烈欢迎
独一无二的Taylor Swift
"Once upon a time, a few mistakes ago "
"I was in your sights, you got me alone "
"You found me, you found me
"You found me-ee-ee-ee-ee
"I guess you didn't care "
"And I guess I liked that
"And when I fell hard, you took a step back "
"Without me, without me
"Without me-ee-ee-ee-ee-ee
"And he's long gone "
"When he's next to me "
"And I realize
"The blame is on me
"'Cause I knew you were trouble "
"When you walked in
"So shame on me now
"Flew me to places I never been "
"Till you put me down, oh
"I knew you were trouble when you walked in "
"Shame on me now
"Flew me to places I never been "
"Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground "
"Oh, oh
"Trouble, trouble, trouble
"No apologies
"He'll never see you cry "
"Pretends he doesn't know that he's the reason why "
"You're drowning, you're drowning "
"You're drown-ee-ee-ee-ee-ing " 916 00:54: 00:54:48,818
"Now, I heard you moved on from whispers on the street "
"A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be "
"Now I see
"Now I see, now I see ee-ee-ee-ee
"He was long gone
"When he met me
"And I realize
"The joke is on me
"Yeah!
"I knew you were trouble when you walked in "
"So shame on me now,
flew me to places i never been
"Till you put me down, oh, I knew you were "
"Trouble when you walked in
"So shame on me now
"Flew me to places I never been "
"Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground "
"Oh, oh
"Trouble, trouble, trouble
"Trouble, trouble "Trouble,
and the saddest fear "
"Comes creeping in
"That you never loved me
"Or her or anyone
"Or anything
"Yeah...
"I knew you were trouble When you walked in "Yeah...
"So shame on me now "
"Flew me to places I never been "
"Never been till you put me down, oh "
"Knew you were trouble when you walked in "
"So shame on me now
"Flew me to places "I never been
"Now I'm lying "
"On the cold hard ground, oh "Oh
"Trouble, trouble, trouble
"Oh, oh
"Trouble, trouble " "Trouble, ah
"Knew you were "
"Trouble when you walked in
"Trouble, trouble, trouble
"Knew you were trouble when you walked in "
"Trouble, trouble, trouble.
进第七首音乐  二  一  走
上吧  宝贝儿们  上上上
来来来
太赞了  赞赞赞
"The applause, applause, applause "
"Give me that thing that I love "
"I'll turn the lights on "
"Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch "
"Give me that thing that I love "
"I'll turn the lights on "
"Put your hands up, make 'em touch "
"Make it real loud...
"A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E "Make it real loud
"Put your hands up, make 'em touch "
"Make it real loud...
"A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E "Make it real loud
"Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch "
"Put your hands up, make ' 'emouch, touch "
"A-p-p-l-a-u-s-e
"Make it real loud
"Put your hands up, make 'em toutoch, uch "
"A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E "Make it real loud
"Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch "
"I live for the applause
"Applause, applause
"I live for the applause-plause "
"Live for the applause-plause... "
2013年走秀圆满落幕
现在要在后台拍个照
大家要拍个合影
任务很艰巨  你们要拍个集体大合影
2013年大合影
你们想要Taylor是吧
对哦  谁能抗拒得了Taylor Swift呢
大家靠近一点
一  二  三
谢谢
太棒了  谢谢  收工咯
最新电影首发 请访问
bt新气息 www.xinqixi.com